A Guide to the Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
- Minute books and ledgers, 1849-1952
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, general ledger (219), 1900-1901 (Volume 210)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, index to real estate (226), 1867-1906 (Volume 211)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, ledger (220), 1902-1911 (Volume 211)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, monthly cash journal (221), 1902-1905 (Volume 212)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, monthly cash journal (222), 1905-1921 (Volume 213)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, monthly cash journal (223), 1922-1928 (Volume 214)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, stock ledger (230), 1906-1927 (Volume 215)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, stock register (230A), 1906-1926 (Volume 216)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, stock transfer book (231B), 1906-1926 (Volume 217)
  - Norfolk Railway and Light Company, stockholders' minute book (235), 1899-1927 (Volume 218)
  - Norfolk Street Railroad Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (244), 1894-1900 (Volume 219)
  - Norfolk Street Railroad Company, cash book (241), 1894-1897 (Volume 220)
  - Norfolk Street Railroad Company, general ledger (239), 1897-1900 (Volume 221)
  - Norfolk Street Railroad Company, journal (240), 1897-1899 (Volume 222)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, cash journal (249), 1904-1906 (Volume 223)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, cash journal (250), 1907-1910 (Volume 224)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, cash journal (251), 1910-1913 (Volume 225)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, cash journal (252), 1913-1915 (Volume 226)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, cash journal (253), 1916-1918 (Volume 227)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, cash journal (254), 1919-1921 (Volume 228)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, cash journal (255), 1922-1924 (Volume 229)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, cash journal (256), 1925-1927 (Volume 230)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, general ledger (248), 1917-1933 (Volume 231)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, ledger (prior to receivership) (259), 1890 (Volume 232)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, minute book (260), 1890-1927 (Volume 233)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, receiver's cash book and journal (257), 1904-1905 (Volume 234)
  - Northside Viaduct Company, receiver's ledger (258), 1903-1906 (Volume 235)
  - Ocean View Hotel Company, minute book (270), 1877-1884 (Volume 235a)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, board of directors' minute book (269A), 1936-1939 (Volume 236)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, board of directors' minute book (269B), 1939-1945 (Volume 237)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, cash book (267), 1937-1939 (Volume 238)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, cash book (268), 1939-1942 (Volume 239)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, ledger (262), 1937 (Volume 240)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, ledger (263), 1939-1945 (Volume 241)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, trustee's cash book (269D), 1933-1934 (Volume 242)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, trustee's ledger (269C), 1933-1936 (Volume 243)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, voucher and journal register (264), 1937-1939 (Volume 244)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, voucher and journal register (265), 1939-1941 (Volume 245)
  - Ocean View Incorporated, voucher and journal register (266), 1941-1945 (Volume 246)
  - Old Dominion Iron and Nailworks, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (273), 1892-1905 (Volume 247)
  - Old Dominion Iron and Nailworks, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (274), 1906-1919 (Volume 248)
  - Old Dominion Iron and Nailworks, stock ledger (272), 1882-1892 (Volume 249)
  - [THERE IS NO VOLUME 250] (Volume 250)
  - Old Dominion Iron and Steel Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (281), 1920-1926 (Volume 251)
  - Old Dominion Iron and Steel Company, cash journal (279), 1919-1926 (Volume 252)
  - Old Dominion Iron and Steel Company, general ledger (278), 1919-1925 (Volume 253)
  - Old Dominion Iron and Steel Company, stock ledger - A to L (282), 1926 (Volume 254)
  - Old Dominion Iron and Steel Company, stock ledger - M to Z (283), 1914-1926 (Volume 255)
  - Old Dominion Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (277), 1901-1906 (Volume 256)
  - Old Dominion Railway Company, cash journal (276), 1902-1906 (Volume 257)
  - Old Dominion Railway Company, general ledger (275), 1902-1906 (Volume 258)
  - Orange Light Company (Orange Coal and Ice Company), board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (40J-1), 1920-1924 (Volume 259)
  - Peninsula Grain Products Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (286), 1920-1926 (Volume 260)
  - Peninsula Grain Products Corporation, cash journal (285), 1919-1925 (Volume 261)
  - Peninsula Grain Products Corporation, ledger (284), 1923-1925 (Volume 262)
  - Piedmont Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (42J-1), 1924-1926 (Volume 263)
  - Piedmont Power Company, cash journal (42B-1), 1924-1926 (Volume 264)
  - Piedmont Traction Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (287), 1897-1898 (Volume 265)
  - Port-Norfolk Electric Railway Company, stockholders' minute book, 1898-1899 (Volume 265a)
  - Portsmouth and Newport News Railway, Ferry and Hotel Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (294), 1896-1899 (Volume 266)
  - Portsmouth and Smithfield Railroad Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (296), 1899-1900 (Volume 267)
  - Portsmouth Electric and Gas Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (293), 1899-1902 (Volume 268)
  - Portsmouth Electric and Gas Company, cash book (292), 1901-1905 (Volume 269)
  - Portsmouth-Norfolk Electric Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book and stock ledger (289), 1892-1898 (Volume 270)
  - Portsmouth-Norfolk Electric Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (291), 1899-1900 (Volume 271)
  - Portsmouth, Pigs Point and Newport News Railway Company, minute book (295), 1896-1900 (Volume 272)
  - Portsmouth Transit Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (297), 1923-1926 (Volume 273)
  - Railway Home Corporation, general ledger (44A-1), 1919-1926 (Volume 274)
  - Railway Home Corporation, minute book (44J-1), 1919-1928 (Volume 275)
  - Railways and Light Company of America, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (297A), 1899-1908 (Volume 276)
  - Railways and Light Company of America, executive committee minute book (297B), 1901-1904 (Volume 277)
  - Rappahannock Electric and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (298), 1903-1923 (Volume 278)
  - Richmond and Chesapeake Bay Railway Company, minute book (299), 1905-1914 (Volume 279)
  - Richmond and Manchester Railway Company, cash journal (302), 1899-1900 (Volume 280)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (330), 1898-1932 (Volume 281)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, cash journal (329), 1902-1904 (Volume 282)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, franchise description of rights-of-way (332), 1901 (Volume 283)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, franchises journal (331), 1901 (Volume 284)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway, general ledger (328), 1902-1903 (Volume 285)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, general ledger (333A), 1904-1909 (Volume 286)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, receiver's record journal (333B), 1904-1906 (Volume 287)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, receiver's record journal (333C), 1906-1908 (Volume 288)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, receiver's record journal (333D), 1909 (Volume 289)
  - Richmond and Petersburg Electric Railway Company, record of legal proceedings and description of rights-of-way (333), 1901 (Volume 290)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (309), 1900-1901 (Volume 291)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, board of directors' minute book (312), 1904 (Volume 291a)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, cash book (307), 1902 (Volume 292)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, cash journal (306), 1902-1904 (Volume 293)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, ledger (327A), 1902 (Volume 294)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, ledger (304), 1902-1904 (Volume 295)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, ledger (318), 1906-1909 (Volume 296)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (cash)(324), 1905-1906 (Volume 297)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (cash)(325), 1906 (Volume 298)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (cash)(326), 1907 (Volume 299)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (journal)(319), 1904-1905 (Volume 300)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (journal)(320), 1905-1906 (Volume 301)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (journal)(317), 1904-1906 (Volume 301a)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (journal)(321), 1906-1907 (Volume 302)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (journal)(322), 1907-1908 (Volume 303)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, receiver's record book (journal)(323), 1908-1909 (Volume 304)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, report of H. B. Boudar and Company (auditors)(313), 1907 (Volume 305)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, stock register (preferred)(314), 1902-1903 (Volume 306)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, board of directors' minute book (311), 1901-1902 (Volume 307)
  - Richmond Passenger and Power Company, stockholders' minute book (310), 1901-1902 (Volume 308)
  - Richmond Railroad and Viaduct Company, ledger (342), 1914-1916 (Volume 309)
  - Richmond Railroad and Viaduct Company, ledger (343), 1914-1916 (Volume 310)
  - Richmond Railroad and Viaduct Company, minutes (345), November 1914-July 1916 (Volume 311)
  - Richmond Railway and Electric Company, cash book (338), 1892-1893 (Volume 312)
  - Richmond Railway and Electric Company, cash book (340), 1898-1900 (Volume 313)
  - Richmond Railway and Electric Company, cash book (339), 1904-1907 (Volume 314)
  - Richmond Railway and Electric Company, journal (335), 1892-1893 (Volume 315)
  - Richmond Railway and Electric Company, journal (337), 1899-1900 (Volume 316)
  - Richmond Railway and Electric Company, ledger (334), 1894-1899 (Volume 317)
  - Synopsis of [Financial] Report of the Richmond Railway and Electric Company, the Richmond and Manchester Railway Company, the Manchester Railway and Improvement Company, the Richmond City and Seven Pines Railway Company, and the Richmond Traction Company, 1896-1867 (Volume 509)
  - Richmond Rapid Transit Company, cash journal (346), 1924-1925 (Volume 318)
  - Richmond Rapid Transit Company, journal (348), 1924-March 1925 (Volume 319)
  - Richmond Rapid Transit Company, journal (349), March-September 1925 (Volume 320)
  - Richmond Rapid Transit Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (354), January 1923-1926 (Volume 321)
  - Richmond Rapid Transit Corporation, vouchers and journal (350), September 1925-1926 (Volume 322)
  - Richmond Traction Company, general ledger (355), 1896-1901 (Volume 322a)
  - Richmond Traction Company, general ledger (356), 1901-1903 (Volume 323)
  - Richmond Traction Company, journal (357), 1895-1897 (Volume 323a)
  - Richmond Traction Company, journal (363), 1904-1906 (Volume 324)
  - Richmond Traction Company, journal (357a), 1904-1909 (Volume 325)
  - Richmond Traction Company, board of directors' minute book (360), 1895-1904 (Volume 326)
  - Richmond Traction Company, stockholders' minute book (361), 1895-1904 (Volume 327)
  - Richmond Traction Company, stock ledger (359), 1895-1902 (Volume 327a)
  - Richmond Viaduct Company, general ledger (367), 1927-1932 (Volume 328)
  - Richmond Viaduct Company, journal (368), 1927 (Volume 329)
  - Richmond Viaduct Company, stockholders' and board of directors' minute book (371), May 1927-December 1933 (Volume 330)
  - Riverside Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (46J-1), 1910-1923 (Volume 331)
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Company, general ledger (372), 1895-1925 (Volume 332)
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Company, general ledger (373), 1915-1921 (Volume 333)
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Company, journal (376), 1895-1910 (Volume 334)
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Company, journal (378), 1915-1917 (Volume 335)
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Company, journal (380), 1924-1925 (Volume 336)
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Company, ledger (375), 1924-1925 (Volume 337)
  - Roanoke Rapids Power Company, stock ledger(386), 1895-1925 (Volume 338)
  - Roanoke River Development Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (395), 1913-1925 (Volume 339)
  - Roanoke River Development Company, journal (391), 1913-1917 (Volume 340)
  - Roanoke River Development Company, journal (392), 1919-1921 (Volume 341)
  - Roanoke River Development Company, journal (393), 1922-1926 (Volume 342)
  - Roanoke River Development Company, register (394), 1913-1922 (Volume 343)
  - Rockbridge Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (47J-2), 1908-1913 (Volume 344)
  - Rockbridge Power Company, ledger (47A-1), 1909-1914 (Volume 345)
  - Rosecliff Development Corporation, minute book (765), 1922-1929 (Volume 346)
  - Sabine Colleries Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (400A), April 1917-March 1929 (Volume 347)
  - Sabine Colleries Corporation, general ledger (396), 1917-1939 (Volume 348)
  - Sabine Colleries Corporation, journal (397), 1917-1921 (Volume 349)
  - Sabine Colleries Corporation, journal (398), 1922-1929 (Volume 350)
  - Sabine Colleries Corporation, vouchers and check register (400), 1917-1926 (Volume 351)
  - Seven Pines Line, journal (301), 1918-1920 (Volume 352)
  - Southside Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (50J-1), 1926 (Volume 353)
  - Southside Railway and Development Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (404), 1899-1901 (Volume 354)
  - Southside Railway and Development Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (405), 1901 (Volume 354a)
  - Southside Railway and Development Company, general ledger (401), 1898-1901 (Volume 355)
  - Southside Railway and Development Company, receiver's record (406), 1905-1906 (Volume 356)
  - Southside Railway and Development Company, receiver's record (408), 1907-1909 (Volume 357)
  - Spotsylvania Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (435), 1914-1925 (Volume 358)
  - Spotsylvania Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (437), 1914-1925 (Volume 359)
  - Spotsylvania Power Company, board of directors' minute book (436), October 1925 (Volume 360)
  - Spotsylvania Power Company, voucher register (432), 1921-1923 (Volume 361)
  - Staunton Lighting Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (51J-1), 1910-1923 (Volume 362)
  - Staunton Lighting Company, journal (51B-2), 1915-1922 (Volume 363)
  - Suburban and City Railway Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (440), 1887-1894 (Volume 364)
  - Suburban and City Railway Company, cash book (439), 1888-1894 (Volume 365)
  - Suburban and City Railway Company, journal (438), 1888-1894 (Volume 366)
  - Suffolk Light and Ice Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (445), 1901-1906 (Volume 367)
  - Suffolk Light and Ice Company, general ledger (442), 1906 (Volume 368)
  - Tidewater Electric Service Company, minute book (754), August 1936-November 1939 (Volume 369)
  - Tidewater Electric Service Company, minute book (755), February 1940-December 1945 (Volume 370)
  - Tidewater Electric Service Company, minute book (756), January 1946-April 1947 (Volume 371)
  - Union Fort Spring Power Company, journal (53B-1), 1931-1936 (Volume 372)
  - Valley Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (54J-1), 1910-1921 (Volume 373)
  - Virginia Carolina Power Company - North Carolina, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (464), 1911-1929 (Volume 374)
  - Virginia Carolina Power Company - North Carolina, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (464a), 1930-1937 (Volume 375)
  - Virginia Carolina Power Company - Virginia, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (463), 1923-1935 (Volume 376)
  - Virginia Carolina Power Company, general ledger (457), 1912-1928 (Volume 377)
  - Virginia Carolina Power Company, journal (459), 1912-1929 (Volume 378)
  - Virginia East Coast Utilities, Inc., minute book (735), 1927-1929 (Volume 379)
  - Virginia East Coast Utilities, Inc., minute book (736), 1930-1934 (Volume 380)
  - Virginia East Coast Utilities, Inc., minute book (737), 1935-1939 (Volume 381)
  - Virginia East Coast Utilities, Inc., minute book (738), 1940-1946 (Volume 382)
  - Virginia East Coast Utilities, Inc., minute book (739), 1947 (Volume 383)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company, journal register no. 1 (B1), January-November 1926 (Volume 384)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company, journal register no. 2 (B2), November 1926-August 1927 (Volume 385)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company, journal register no. 3 (B3), August 1927-January 1929 (Volume 386)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company, monthly president's letters, 1940 (Volume 387)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company, monthly president's letters, 1941 (Volume 388)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company (Norfolk Division), journal register no. 2 (B1-2), January 1931-October 1934 (Volume 389)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company (Norfolk Division), journal register no. 3 (B1-1), November-December 1934 (Volume 390)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company (Richmond Division), journal register no. 5 (B5), July 1931-February 1934 (Volume 391)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company (Richmond Division), journal register no. 6 (B6), March-December 1934 (Volume 392)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company (Richmond Division), journal register no. 7 (B7), January 1935-December 1936 (Volume 393)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, cash book and voucher register (473), September 1927-October 1928 (Volume 394)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, cash book and voucher register (474), October 1928-March 1931 (Volume 395)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, cash book and voucher register (475), April 1931-August 1933 (Volume 396)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, cash book and voucher register (476), September 1933-June 1936 (Volume 397)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484G), 1927-1930 (Volume 398)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484H), 1931 (Volume 399)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484I), 1932 (Volume 400)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484J), 1933 (Volume 401)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484K), 1934 (Volume 402)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484L), 1935 (Volume 403)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484M), 1936 (Volume 404)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484N), 1937 (Volume 405)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484O), 1938 (Volume 406)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484P), 1939 (Volume 407)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484R), 1940 (Volume 408)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484S), 1941 (Volume 409)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484T), 1942 (Volume 410)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484U), 1943 (Volume 411)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company - Benefit Association, minutes and correspondence (484V), 1944 (Volume 412)
  - Virginia Electric Company, cash book (466), 1899 (Volume 413)
  - Virginia Electric Company, general ledger (465), 1898 (Volume 414)
  - Virginia Electric Company, board of directors' minutes (469), 1898-1899 (Volume 415)
  - Virginia Electric Company, stockholders' minutes (468), 1898 (Volume 416)
  - Virginia Electric Company, subscribers' minutes (467), 1898 (Volume 417)
  - Virginia Electric Railway and Development Company, board of directors' minutes (492), 1901-1902 (Volume 418)
  - Virginia Electric Railway and Development Company, general ledger (485), 1898-1902 (Volume 419)
  - Virginia Electric Railway and Development Company, journal (486), 1901-1902 (Volume 420)
  - Virginia Electric Railway and Development Company, stockholders' minutes (491), 1898-1902 (Volume 421)
  - Virginia Internal Improvement Company, board of directors' minutes (493), 1901 (Volume 422)
  - Virginia Light and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute books (498-499), 1905-1914 (Volume 423, 423a)
  - Virginia Light and Power Company, general ledger (494), 1910-1914 (Volume 424)
  - Virginia Light and Power Company, journal (495), 1908-1913 (Volume 425)
  - Virginia Light and Power Company, journal (496), 1913-1914 (Volume 426)
  - Virginia Northern Ice Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (56J-1), March 1920-November 1932 (Volume 427)
  - Virginia Northern Ice Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (56J-2), December 1932-December 1937 (Volume 428)
  - Virginia Northern Ice Corporation, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (56J-3), 1938-1943 (Volume 429)
  - Virginia Northern Ice Corporation, ledger (56A-4), 1937-1939 (Volume 430)
  - Virginia Northern Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (57J-1), 1924-1926 (Volume 431)
  - Virginia Northern Power Company, ledger (57A-2), November 1925-February 1926 (Volume 432)
  - Virginia Northern Power Company, sub-ledger operating detail (56G-2), January-March 1926 (Volume 433)
  - Virginia Passenger and Power Company, board of directors' minute book (520), 1902-1903 (Volume 434)
  - Virginia Passenger and Power Company, board of directors' and stockholders' minute book (521), 1903-1904 (Volume 435)
  - Virginia Passenger and Power Company, common stock ledger (517), 1903 (Volume 436)
  - Virginia Passenger and Power Company, journal - receiver's record (527), 1906-1907 (Volume 437)
  - Virginia Passenger and Power Company, preferred stock ledger (518), 1903 (Volume 438)
  - Virginia Passenger and Power Company, receiver's records (524), 1906-1909 (Volume 439)
  - Virginia Passenger and Power Company, stockholders' minute book (519), 1902-1903 (Volume 440)
  - Virginia Public Service Company, annual report to the State Corporate Commission, 1937-1939 (Volume 440a)
  - Virginia Public Service Company, annual report to the State Corporate Commission, 1940-1942 (Volume 441)
  - Virginia Public Service Generating Company, board of directors' minute book (58J-1), 1939-1940 (Volume 442)
  - Virginia Public Service Generating Company, board of directors' minute book (58J-2), 1941-1942 (Volume 443)
  - Virginia Railway and Power Company, authorized expenditures (622), 1914-1916 (Volume 444)